Employee Number SP01zs6dg
Designation Product Development
Development Group 2
Planning, Team A
Name
Katase Shiori
Product Development
Group 2
Character Marketing Outline
Group 2, Team A
Shinozaki Takuma
That ought to do it.
Very good, Shinozaki-san!
S-Senpai...
Is your meeting over already?
Yep. It didn't take as long as I thought.
And it looks like you finished
everything I asked you to do, too.
Excellent work!
Aw, no...
It was just regular work.
Nothing worth that kind of praise.
Is there something wrong
with praising regular work?
I actually appreciate it a lot.
Very good!
You know, I really am proud
of you, Shinozaki-san!
There's a Senpai where I work...
who is tiny, and cute.
My Tiny Senpai
#01 My Senpai Is Small and Cute
Development Group 2
Planning, Team A
Shinozaki Takuma
(1st Year of Employment)
What're you doing, Senpai?
Sh-Shinozaki-san! Good morning.
Good morning.
It's just, well...
I saw a cat go into those bushes.
Development Group 2
Planning, Team A
Katase Shiori
(3rd Year of Employment)
I thought it might
come back out if I called to it...
That's what you were doing?!
It was the cutest thing you ever saw!
A tiny brown kitty, about this big...
Really fluffy and soft!
I already know you are, though.
I was talking about the cat.
Right! Of course! The cat!
Oh, look at the time!
Let's get moving, Shinozaki-san!
R-Right!
Development Group 2
Team A Manager
Akina Chihiro
(5th year of Employment)
Manager.
I sent the plan for our entry
into the project competition,
so please check it, when you get a chance.
Wait, already? There's still
a while until the deadline.
I know! But since we'll need to
incorporate input from the client,
the sooner we get it checked,
the sooner I can make those adjustments.
Makes sense. Well done, Katase-san.
I appreciate how timely you are.
Nice one, Senpai.
This is all normal stuff.
I'm a grown-up, after all!
I have to say, desk work really does
a number on the back and shoulders...
My whole body feels creaky.
It's even worse when you're
on the computer all the time.
Definitely...
My shoulders can really seize up on me, too.
I think there might be more to it
than just work, in that regard...
It's the kind of thing that
makes you want a massage, huh?
Oh, what a great idea! I'd love that!
Wait... did I just stumble into a mildly
erotic situation involving a massage?
Want me to rub them?
Would you?
Right there... It feels... so good...!
If you keep that up... I'll...
Something wrong?
N-No, nothing at all!
I get stiff shoulders, too, so I was thinking
about maybe getting a massage myself.
Sounds like a case where a hardworking
kohai needs some senpai encouragement!
Aw, come on, I couldn't ask you to do that...
Don't you worry about it.
Just don't fall asleep
from being too comfy, okay?
Squeezey, squeezey, squeezey, squeezey...
Senpai's tiny hands are all over my shoulders!
I'm getting squeezed!
She's kneading me like dough!
It's like I'm in the world's
comfiest theme park!
Shinozaki-san, you're so... hard, and big...
I don't know if my hands
can make you feel good.
Senpai, uh, I think that's enough!
Did it feel good?
Yes! Maybe a little too good.
Er, forget I said anything! Really!
"And that is my proposal."
Okay, hopefully that should work.
Maybe I should run through it again...
"I'm Shinozaki Takuma
with Dev Group 2's Team A."
"My proposal involves the upcoming anniversary
of our company's main mascot
character, Meowtaro, which—"
What's that you've got there?
S-Senpai!
Did I scare you?
The new employee project
presentations are tomorrow,
so I was practicing during my free time.
That takes me back!
I remember what it was like.
And so, by arranging a collaboration
between popular sweets brands
and our company's mascot character, Meowtaro,
I believe we could cultivate customers
in a new demographic.
Meowtaro Collabo
Currently popular sweets
Er, uh, pardon me...!
I made some goofs
with the materials for my proposal.
But as you can see, I'm still here,
so relax and give your best shot!
What a random bit of encouragement!
Thank you, Senpai.
I just have this tendency to get
super nervous when it's showtime...
They say writing the kanji for "person" in your
hand and pretending to swallow it helps.
What do you think?
It's probably just a superstition...
Although one theory says the palm
has certain pressure points,
and by tracing the kanji for "person"
you can press them for a relaxation effect—
Shinozaki-san!
Something to relax you.
Specially made by your Senpai,
it's the kanji for "person."
I hope you enjoy it!
S-So close! Senpai's tiny hand
is right in front of me!
I-It almost seems like a waste to eat it!
I can always make more.
So, by all means, eat up!
She is so wifely, it's killing me!
Th-Then, in that case, don't mind if I do...
Uh, er, did my breath tickle?
Oh, no, it's f-fine!
H-How do you feel?
Better! I think I can do this.
Thank you so much, Senpai.
I'll be looking forward to another
tomorrow, before my presentation.
Not a problem! I'll be there.
Yamagishi-san.
Development Group 2
Team B, Designer
Yamagishi Aiko
(1st Year of Employment)
Will you be coming to the
end-of-month drinking party?
Oh, you bet!
That's plus one, then.
You're organizing, Shinozaki-kun?
Yeah, I drew the short stick.
Hey, Hayakawa, you coming to
the end of month drinking party?
Development Group 2
Team A, Designer
Hayakawa Chinatsu
(1st Year of Employment)
I'll pass.
Again? Sociable as ever, I see.
Quit whining. I attended once, remember?
Yeah, once. The first time.
Stare...
Once is plenty, isn't it?
Staaare...
Are you two going out?
What?!
It's just, Shinozaki-kun seems
weirdly frank with you, Hayakawa-san.
Th-That's not it! Hayakawa...san
here is just a childhood friend!
Yeah, exactly! We just grew up near each other!
Dating her? Is that really how it looks?
Shinozaki-san.
Do you and Hayakawa-san get along?
You, too, Senpai?!
It's less that and more...
We were neighbors,
and we attended preschool,
elementary, and middle school together.
Then we just happened to end up
working at the same company.
It's kinda like we're cursed.
You seemed to be pretty friendly, though.
Wait, what? Is she jealous?
No, come on, Senpai would never...
It's really nothing special.
Sure, we chat casually...
I'm jealous.
S-S-Senpai?! She just said she was jealous!
I did hear that, didn't I?!
And she does seem to be kind of sulky...
Senpai's... jealous?
That'd mean she... about me... for real?
Shinozaki-san.
I...
I... well...
I want to be friends with Hayakawa-san, too.
I've always thought she seems rather neat,
but we've never really had
a chance to connect outside of work.
If you wouldn't mind,
could you maybe introduce me...?
That's what she meant?!
What's wrong?
Just regretting my arrogance, that's all.
Welcome!
A party of three? I'll show you to your seats.
Y'know, I tend to attract cats for some reason.
I can tell.
My Tiny Senpai!
This cardboard box is actually pretty heavy.
Let me get that for you, Senpai!
I'm so sorry...
No, no, don't let it bother you.
These kinds of things happen.
Just let me know if you need any more help.
Thank you so much.
Shinozaki-san.
Did something happen?
There was a bit of a mix up with some data...
But it should be fine, now.
40th Anniversary
You never seem to get mad at people, Senpai.
You think so?
I mean, just now...
If someone's already upset
about their mistakes,
I'm not going to make it worse for them.
Besides, you can scold someone
without getting mad at them.
More importantly, Shinozaki-san!
Yes?!
You haven't been reporting in enough, lately!
I haven't?!
Did I... screw up with work somehow?
And wait...
Am I getting scolded, right now?
Uh, well... I...
When you work hard,
I expect you to tell me about it.
J-Just when I work hard?
Exactly!
I don't want to miss your efforts,
especially when you put your heart into them.
If this is supposed to be discipline,
then sign me up!
It's a senpai's duty...
to praise a job well done.
Okay, next time I work hard on something...
I'll try to make sure and notice, too.
I appreciate that.
Come on, we're back
to the office and back to work!
Right! Wait up, Senpai!
It's getting late,
but I wanna keep going a bit longer...
Let's finish this up, at least.
I bought two by mistake.
You're welcome to one.
Thanks so much!
Oh, I should pay you...
No, it's fine, don't worry.
I'm forcing something off onto my subordinate.
Think of it as an abuse of authority!
Best abuse of authority ever!
Are you still not finished for today?
Well, I was just trying to
get to a good place to stop...
I'll help you out!
But, I couldn't ask you to
trouble yourself, Senpai...
It's a senpai's duty to help a kohai in need!
Besides,
once we're done, I'm going to abuse
my authority and treat you to dinner!
They made a sequel to
the best abuse of authority ever!
Th-then I'd appreciate the help.
Sure!
That was faster than I thought!
Only because of you. Thanks again, Senpai.
I'll pay for dinner!
No, not happening. I'm paying.
No, me!
It'll be me.
Me!
It's still a bit cold at night.
Come on, let's hurry to the restaurant.
Sh-Shinozaki-san?!
Please, just wear it.
B-But...
Put your arms through the sleeves, please.
But I... I'll be fine...
No, you won't.
Y'know, you don't need to have
authority to abuse your power...
I-I'll keep that in mind.
There should be plenty of places open still.
Okay.
Um, aren't you cold, Shinozaki-san?
Nope. I'm okay.
This jacket he lent me is really warm...
I guess because he was
just wearing it, but still...
Something about the size and the warmth...
makes it feel like he's hugging me.
Wh-What in the world am I thinking?!
U-um...
I-I don't know...
if I can continue wearing this...
What happened?!
You can have it back!
But...
W-we're almost at the restaurant, so...
And besides,
we're close to the office...
What if someone saw?
Good point.
I'm sorry. I should have considered that.
No, no, I appreciate you letting me wear it!
Come on, let's head in.
I'm feeling hungry!
Right.
Odo Eatery
Welcome!
Party of two? I'll show you to your seats.
The jacket smells like Senpai,
and that's a great smell!
Something wrong?
I-It's nothing!
S-Since it's nice and warm in here,
I think I'll take this off.
What should I order...?
There're so many options,
I don't know where to start.
You can take your time to decide.
Have you made up your mind, Shinozaki-san?
I think I have, yes.
Then, I better decide, fast!
You can take your time, really!
Okay, I've got it!
Press button for service
I'll be right there!
I'll take the miso-glazed beef tongue
and mixed vegetable stew dinner.
And a fluffy soy milk pudding for dessert.
I'll have the saikyo-yaki
cooked mackerel dinner.
That'll be enough.
What about dessert?
Pudding is really good, y'know!
I'm a big fan, it's so soft, and sweet,
and just plain makes you happy!
I'll take one, too, then.
Pudding, pudding, more pudding!
Understood.
It'll be just a moment.
Senpai, I wanna thank you for your help.
And not just for today.
What other day?
I managed to make it through my project
proposal without clamming up, thanks to you.
No, no...
It went well because
you worked hard, Shinozaki-san.
I just helped out a tiny bit!
Besides, I'm obviously going to help
a kohai who could use it.
Because I'm your senpai!
W-Well, I appreciate all that help!
Certainly.
Although...
Don't try and push yourself
to work overtime like today, okay?
Working hard is good,
but overwork is not. Okay?
Right!
Here you are.
Saikyo-yaki cooked mackerel,
and a miso-glazed beef tongue stew.
Please, enjoy.
Come on, let's eat.
We'll have a nutritious meal,
and then give it our best at work tomorrow!
Right!
Time to eat!
Hot!
Are you okay?
Y-Yeah...
Sensitive to hot food like a cat, too, huh?
What do you mean, "too"?
Oh, never mind me!
Good morning, Senpai.
Good morning, Shinozaki-san.
Calling out to another cat?
Yes, indeed I was!
I heard it meowing a second ago...
Did you hear that?! It answered me!
Sure.
That was deeper than before, though.
Maybe there's a second cat?
You! You! I can't believe you made fun of me!
S-Sorry! I didn't think
you'd react like that...
As punishment, for today,
you have to be kitty Shinozaki!
Kitty Shinozaki...?
I expect you to meow in response!
M... Meow.
Y'know, this might be too much...
Excuse me?
It's kind of embarrassing—
These are orders from your senpai!
Okay...
Do you understand?! You respond with "meow!"
Good morning, Manager.
Oh, good morning, Hayakawa-san.
Meow!
You look happy. Something good happen?
Just glad that my team is getting long!
They are?
All right, Meowzaki, we're going to work!
Right, Senpai!
You're supposed to say "Meow!" Okay?
M-Meow!
Let's give it our best today, Meowzaki!